

Front-End Developer

Email: chiani.farimah@yahoo.com

DoB: 1999-05-24

Mobile: (+98)9138220587

Marital Status: Single

Website: https://farimahchiani.github.io/

Address: Isfahan, Iran

Profile Summary

I am Farimah Chiani, a graduated software engineering and have a lot of work experiences in the field of UI Designing, front-end developing (WordPress, Woocomerce, Elementor, Visual Composer, Joomla, Angular, Angular Material, Ag-Grid, HTML, Tailwind, SASS, CSS, Bootstrap, Material UI, TypeScript, JavaScript, JQuey, ReactJS and etc).

It should also be mentioned that I am a mid-level programmer and I am working towards my progress with my experience and knowledge and I am ready to learn new tips and methods.

Some examples of my work:

https://farimahchiani.github.io/

https://nikanprofile.com/

https://tebsaba.com/

https://masihghasemilawyer.ir/

https://rajaeipanah.ir/

https://www.1reportage.com/

https://neginrose.com/

https://www.sayehban.com/

Skills



Work Experience

Frontend طراحی سایت

Nexus

Isfahan, Iran

February 2024 - Present

Tasks and Achievements

Implementation and optimization of WordPress sites.

Frontend Developer

Pishgaman Khalagh Danesh Chista

Isfahan, Iran

December 2022 - April 2023

Tasks and Achievements

In this company, I worked on the company's own sites in a project-oriented manner. There, I worked on sites with vue.js, javascript, jquery and wordpress.

Ui & Ux Designer

Noroweb

Isfahan, Iran

February 2021 - March 2022

Tasks and Achievements

In this company, I did the ui design of the sites.

Frontend Developer

Taban Soft

Isfahan, Iran

April 2023 - February 2024

Tasks and Achievements

In this company, I implement the design and development of the admin and management panel by Angular.

Frontend Developer

Pooneh Media

Isfahan, Iran

March 2022 - September 2022

Tasks and Achievements

In this company, I used html, scss, css, javascript and jquey to create front sites.

Education

Bachelor of Software Engineering

Branch: Computer

Institute/University: Azad University of Isfahan

Isfahan, Iran

2018 - 2020

GPA: 17

Associate in Software

Branch: Computer

Institute/University: Isfahan Sepahan University

Isfahan, Iran

2016 - 2018

GPA: 18.18

_	language					
Persian						
Native						
English language						
Intermediate						
	Social Network					
in farimah-chiani-664923257	7	FarimahChiani	0	farimah.chiani	0	farimah-chian
			Res	search		
Farimah Chiani Portfolio						
Publisher: Farimah Chiani						
Link: https://farimahchiani.github	o.io/					
	Portfolio					
My Portfolio						

For: Farimah Chiani

Link: https://farimahchiani.github.io/